{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Entrepreneur",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Prelims Reviewer Pro Max",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Week-1",
      "Week-2",
      "Week-3",
      "Week-4",
      "Week-5"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the relevance of entrepreneurship where one of the benefits an entrepreneur gets is to develop his managerial skills?",
      "answer": "Development of Managerial Capabilities",
      "choices": [
        "Creation of Organizations",
        "Improving Standard of Living",
        "Means of Economic Development",
        "Development of Managerial Capabilities"
      ],
      "reference": "Relevance of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the relevance of entrepreneurship which means that because of it many organizations will exist?",
      "answer": "Creation of Organizations",
      "choices": [
        "Development of Managerial Capabilities",
        "Improving Standard of Living",
        "Means of Economic Development",
        "Creation of Organizations"
      ],
      "reference": "Relevance of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the relevance of entrepreneurship that can lift up the economic status of an individual?",
      "answer": "Improving Standard of Living",
      "choices": [
        "Development of Managerial Capabilities",
        "Creation of Organizations",
        "Means of Economic Development",
        "Improving Standard of Living"
      ],
      "reference": "Relevance of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the relevance of entrepreneurship where not only the life of the entrepreneur is improved but also the society where the business is located?",
      "answer": "Means of Economic Development",
      "choices": [
        "Development of Managerial Capabilities",
        "Creation of Organizations",
        "Improving Standard of Living",
        "Means of Economic Development"
      ],
      "reference": "Relevance of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was derived from the French verb entreprendre, which means “to undertake?”",
      "answer": "Entrepreneur",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurship",
        "Enterprise",
        "Innovators",
        "Entrepreneur"
      ],
      "reference": "Concept of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the process called when an enterprise is created by an entrepreneur?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurship",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneur",
        "Enterprise",
        "Innovators",
        "Entrepreneurship"
      ],
      "reference": "Concept of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who are innovators?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Teacher",
        "Researcher",
        "Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Concept of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who are willing to take the risks and generate unique ideas that can provide profitable solutions to the needs of the market and the society?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Teacher",
        "Researcher",
        "Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Concept of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor is doing things even before being told?",
      "answer": "Initiative",
      "choices": [
        "Proactive",
        "Problem Solver",
        "Perseverance",
        "Initiative"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means he can classify opportunities and seize it?",
      "answer": "Proactive",
      "choices": [
        "Initiative",
        "Problem Solver",
        "Perseverance",
        "Proactive"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means he can retain good relations with other people?",
      "answer": "Problem Solver",
      "choices": [
        "Initiative",
        "Proactive",
        "Perseverance",
        "Problem Solver"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means he will pursue things to get done regardless of challenges?",
      "answer": "Perseverance",
      "choices": [
        "Initiative",
        "Proactive",
        "Problem Solver",
        "Perseverance"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means that he can entice people to buy even if they don’t want to?",
      "answer": "Persuasion",
      "choices": [
        "A Planner",
        "Risk-taker",
        "Proactive",
        "Persuasion"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means he makes plans before doing things and does not fail to monitor it?",
      "answer": "A Planner",
      "choices": [
        "Persuasion",
        "Risk-taker",
        "Proactive",
        "A Planner"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What personality factor means that he is willing to gamble but he will calculate it first?",
      "answer": "Risk-taker",
      "choices": [
        "Persuasion",
        "A Planner",
        "Proactive",
        "Risk-taker"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What factors include political, climate, legal system, economic and social conditions and market situations?",
      "answer": "Environmental Factors",
      "choices": [
        "Personality Factors",
        "Core Competencies",
        "Common Competencies",
        "Environmental Factors"
      ],
      "reference": "Factors Affecting Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur must be firm in making decisions?",
      "answer": "Decisive",
      "choices": [
        "Communicator",
        "Leader",
        "Opportunity seeker",
        "Decisive"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur must have a convincing power?",
      "answer": "Communicator",
      "choices": [
        "Decisive",
        "Leader",
        "Opportunity seeker",
        "Communicator"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur must have the charisma to be obeyed by his employees?",
      "answer": "Leader",
      "choices": [
        "Decisive",
        "Communicator",
        "Opportunity seeker",
        "Leader"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur must have the ability to be the first to see business chances?",
      "answer": "Opportunity seeker",
      "choices": [
        "Decisive",
        "Communicator",
        "Leader",
        "Opportunity seeker"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur can control a situation by making things happen or by preparing for possible future problems?",
      "answer": "Proactive",
      "choices": [
        "Risk Taker",
        "Innovative",
        "Leader",
        "Proactive"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means an entrepreneur has the courage to pursue business ideas?",
      "answer": "Risk Taker",
      "choices": [
        "Proactive",
        "Innovative",
        "Leader",
        "Risk Taker"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What common competency means the entrepreneur has big business ideas and he does not stop improving and thinking of new worthwhile ideas for his business?",
      "answer": "Innovative",
      "choices": [
        "Proactive",
        "Risk Taker",
        "Leader",
        "Innovative"
      ],
      "reference": "Common Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What core competency is an economic activity because it involves the creation and operation of an enterprise with a view to creating value or wealth by ensuring optimum utilization of limited resources?",
      "answer": "Economic and Dynamic Activity",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative",
        "Profit Potential",
        "Risk bearing",
        "Economic and Dynamic Activity"
      ],
      "reference": "Core Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What core competency means the entrepreneur constantly looks for new ideas, thus he needs to be creative?",
      "answer": "Innovative",
      "choices": [
        "Economic and Dynamic Activity",
        "Profit Potential",
        "Risk bearing",
        "Innovative"
      ],
      "reference": "Core Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What core competency means the entrepreneur can be compensated by his profit coming from the operation?",
      "answer": "Profit Potential",
      "choices": [
        "Economic and Dynamic Activity",
        "Innovative",
        "Risk bearing",
        "Profit Potential"
      ],
      "reference": "Core Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What core competency means the entrepreneur needs to gamble but wise enough to offset the risk?",
      "answer": "Risk bearing",
      "choices": [
        "Economic and Dynamic Activity",
        "Innovative",
        "Profit Potential",
        "Risk bearing"
      ],
      "reference": "Core Competencies in Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are those who always make new things by thinking of new ideas?",
      "answer": "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs have the ability to think newer, better and more economical ideas?",
      "answer": "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are those who don’t create new things but only follow the ideas of other entrepreneurs?",
      "answer": "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are skeptical about changes to be made in the organization?",
      "answer": "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs don’t initiate but follow only after they are satisfied?",
      "answer": "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are those who live on the labor of others?",
      "answer": "Drone Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are die-hard conservatives even ready to suffer the loss of business?",
      "answer": "Drone Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Fabian Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of entrepreneurs are those who initiate changes and drive social innovation and transformation in the various fields such as education, health, human rights, environment and enterprise development?",
      "answer": "Social Entrepreneurs",
      "choices": [
        "Innovative Entrepreneurs",
        "Imitating Entrepreneurs",
        "Drone Entrepreneurs",
        "Social Entrepreneurs"
      ],
      "reference": "Types of Entrepreneurs",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What career opportunity means that with the expertise of in the field of entrepreneurship, he can be a very good source of advices to other entrepreneurs and would be businessmen?",
      "answer": "Business Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Teacher",
        "Researcher",
        "Sales",
        "Business Consultant"
      ],
      "reference": "Career Opportunities of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What career opportunity means a graduate of an entrepreneurship can use his knowledge in teaching?",
      "answer": "Teacher",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Researcher",
        "Sales",
        "Teacher"
      ],
      "reference": "Career Opportunities of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What career opportunity means the entrepreneur can be employed as a researcher by an enterprise?",
      "answer": "Researcher",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Teacher",
        "Sales",
        "Researcher"
      ],
      "reference": "Career Opportunities of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What career opportunity means the entrepreneurship graduate can apply as a salesman?",
      "answer": "Sales",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Teacher",
        "Researcher",
        "Sales"
      ],
      "reference": "Career Opportunities of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What career opportunity means the entrepreneur being expert in the field, can be employed as a business reporter?",
      "answer": "Business Reporter",
      "choices": [
        "Business Consultant",
        "Teacher",
        "Researcher",
        "Business Reporter"
      ],
      "reference": "Career Opportunities of Entrepreneurship",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What allows the entrepreneur to see things in a very positive and optimistic way in the midst of difficult situation?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurial mind frame",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurial heart flame",
        "Entrepreneurial gut game",
        "Passion",
        "Entrepreneurial mind frame"
      ],
      "reference": "Essentials in Entrepreneur's Opportunity Seeking",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the entrepreneur's driven passion, where they are attracted to discover satisfaction in the act and process of discovery?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurial heart flame",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurial mind frame",
        "Entrepreneurial gut game",
        "Passion",
        "Entrepreneurial heart flame"
      ],
      "reference": "Essentials in Entrepreneur's Opportunity Seeking",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the great desire of an entrepreneur to achieve his/her goals?",
      "answer": "Passion",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurial mind frame",
        "Entrepreneurial heart flame",
        "Entrepreneurial gut game",
        "Passion"
      ],
      "reference": "Essentials in Entrepreneur's Opportunity Seeking",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the ability of the entrepreneur of being intuitive?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurial gut game",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurial mind frame",
        "Entrepreneurial heart flame",
        "Entrepreneurial Intuition",
        "Entrepreneurial gut game"
      ],
      "reference": "Essentials in Entrepreneur's Opportunity Seeking",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another term for the ability of the entrepreneur of being intuitive?",
      "answer": "Intuition",
      "choices": [
        "Entrepreneurial mind frame",
        "Entrepreneurial heart flame",
        "Entrepreneurial gut game",
        "Intuition"
      ],
      "reference": "Essentials in Entrepreneur's Opportunity Seeking",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes the weather conditions?",
      "answer": "Climate",
      "choices": [
        "Natural resources",
        "Wildlife",
        "Physical environment",
        "Climate"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes minerals, forests, water, and fertile land that occur in nature and can be used for economic gain?",
      "answer": "Natural resources",
      "choices": [
        "Climate",
        "Wildlife",
        "Physical environment",
        "Natural resources"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes all mammals, birds, reptiles, fish, etc., that live in the wild?",
      "answer": "Wildlife",
      "choices": [
        "Climate",
        "Natural resources",
        "Physical environment",
        "Wildlife"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes all the laws, rules, and regulations that govern business practices as well as the permits, approvals, and licenses necessary to operate the business?",
      "answer": "Political forces",
      "choices": [
        "Economic forces",
        "Sociocultural forces",
        "Technological environment",
        "Political forces"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes forces such as income level and employment rate?",
      "answer": "Economic forces",
      "choices": [
        "Political forces",
        "Sociocultural forces",
        "Technological environment",
        "Economic forces"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes customs, lifestyles and values that characterize a society?",
      "answer": "Sociocultural forces",
      "choices": [
        "Political forces",
        "Economic forces",
        "Technological environment",
        "Sociocultural forces"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes new inventions and technology innovations?",
      "answer": "Technological environment",
      "choices": [
        "Political forces",
        "Economic forces",
        "Sociocultural forces",
        "Technological environment"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What arises when changes happen in the external environment?",
      "answer": "Entrepreneurial ideas",
      "choices": [
        "Technological discovery",
        "People's interest",
        "Past experiences",
        "Entrepreneurial ideas"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the physical environment, societal environment, and industry environment where the business operates?",
      "answer": "External environment",
      "choices": [
        "Internal environment",
        "Competitive environment",
        "Market environment",
        "External environment"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What sees the possibility of business opportunities in any new discovery or because of the use of latest technology?",
      "answer": "A person with entrepreneurial interest",
      "choices": [
        "A government official",
        "A regular consumer",
        "A past employee",
        "A person with entrepreneurial interest"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are also good sources of ideas from the government?",
      "answer": "Priorities, projects, programs, and policies",
      "choices": [
        "Technological discoveries",
        "People's interests",
        "Past experiences",
        "Priorities, projects, programs, and policies"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are a rich source of entrepreneurial ideas related to people?",
      "answer": "The interest, hobbies, and preferences of people",
      "choices": [
        "Government policies",
        "Technological advancements",
        "Past experiences",
        "The interest, hobbies, and preferences of people"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What may lead to the opening of related business enterprise based on a person's history?",
      "answer": "The expertise and skills developed by a person",
      "choices": [
        "Government programs",
        "People's interests",
        "Technological discoveries",
        "The expertise and skills developed by a person"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What source of opportunity comes from the expertise and skills developed by a person who has worked in a particular field?",
      "answer": "Past experiences",
      "choices": [
        "Technological discovery and advancement",
        "Government’s thrust, programs, and policies",
        "People’s interest",
        "Past experiences"
      ],
      "reference": "Sources of Opportunities",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the act or process of trying to get or win something?",
      "answer": "Competition",
      "choices": [
        "Rivalry",
        "Substitute",
        "Bargaining",
        "Competition"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who are the ones that pay cash in exchange to your goods and services?",
      "answer": "Buyers",
      "choices": [
        "Suppliers",
        "Competitors",
        "New entrants",
        "Buyers"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is defined as the one who enters something?",
      "answer": "A new entrant",
      "choices": [
        "A buyer",
        "A supplier",
        "A competitor",
        "A new entrant"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a state or situation in which people or groups are competing with each other?",
      "answer": "Rivalry",
      "choices": [
        "Competition",
        "Substitution",
        "Supply",
        "Rivalry"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is anything that takes the place or function of another?",
      "answer": "Substitute",
      "choices": [
        "Rivalry",
        "Competition",
        "Supply",
        "Substitute"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who are the ones that provide something that is needed or wanted?",
      "answer": "Suppliers",
      "choices": [
        "Buyers",
        "Competitors",
        "New entrants",
        "Suppliers"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another name for the Forces of Competition Model?",
      "answer": "Five forces of competition",
      "choices": [
        "Sources of Opportunities",
        "Entrepreneurial Process",
        "Essentials in Seeking",
        "Five forces of competition"
      ],
      "reference": "Forces of Competition Model",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the means by which the exchange of goods and services takes place as a result of buyers and sellers being in contact with one another?",
      "answer": "Market",
      "choices": [
        "Value Proposition",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Target Market",
        "Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a business or marketing statement that summarizes why a consumer should buy a company's product or use its service?",
      "answer": "Value Proposition",
      "choices": [
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Market Targeting",
        "Customer Requirements",
        "Value Proposition"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to how you sell your product or services to your customer?",
      "answer": "Unique Selling Proposition",
      "choices": [
        "Value Proposition",
        "Market Targeting",
        "Customer Requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition"
      ],
      "reference": "Market and Propositions",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a stage in market identification process that aims to determine the buyers with common needs and characteristics?",
      "answer": "Market Targeting",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Market Targeting"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the market segment that an entrepreneurial venture intends to serve?",
      "answer": "Prospect customers",
      "choices": [
        "Target Market",
        "Buyers",
        "Suppliers",
        "Prospect customers"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market divides the total market according to geographical location?",
      "answer": "Geographic segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Geographic segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided based on consumers?",
      "answer": "Demographic Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided in terms of what customers think and believe?",
      "answer": "Psychological Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What method for segmenting the market is divided according to customers' behavior patterns as they interact with a company?",
      "answer": "Behavioral Segmentation",
      "choices": [
        "Geographic segmentation",
        "Demographic Segmentation",
        "Psychological Segmentation",
        "Behavioral Segmentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Segmentation",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the specific characteristics that customers need from a product or a service?",
      "answer": "Customer requirements",
      "choices": [
        "Service Requirement",
        "Output Requirement",
        "Value Proposition",
        "Customer requirements"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement consists of elements like on-time delivery, service with a smile, and easy-payment?",
      "answer": "Service Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Output Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Service Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement encompasses all aspects of how a customer expects to be treated while purchasing a product?",
      "answer": "Service Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Output Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Unique Selling Proposition",
        "Service Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of customer requirement can take the form of product specifications like the loudness and clarity of a pair of speakers?",
      "answer": "Output Requirement",
      "choices": [
        "Service Requirement",
        "Customer requirements",
        "Value Proposition",
        "Output Requirement"
      ],
      "reference": "Customer Requirements",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the approximate number of sellers and buyers in a particular market?",
      "answer": "Market Size",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Served Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size answers the question \"how big is the universe\"?",
      "answer": "Total Available Market",
      "choices": [
        "Served Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Total Available Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size answers the question \"how many can I reach with my sales channel\"?",
      "answer": "Served Available Market",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Target Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Served Available Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the market size for a startup answers the question \"who will be the most likely buyers\"?",
      "answer": "Target Market",
      "choices": [
        "Total Available Market",
        "Served Available Market",
        "Market Size",
        "Target Market"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Size",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the process of gathering, analyzing and interpreting the information about the products or the services to be offered for sale to the potential consumers in the market?",
      "answer": "Market Research",
      "choices": [
        "Data Collection",
        "Survey",
        "Interview",
        "Market Research"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Research and Data Collection",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most valuable tool in any type of research study?",
      "answer": "Data Collection",
      "choices": [
        "Market Research",
        "Survey",
        "Interview",
        "Data Collection"
      ],
      "reference": "Market Research and Data Collection",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the most common way to gather primary research with the use of questionnaires or interview schedule?",
      "answer": "Surveys",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Surveys"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is one of the most reliable and credible ways of getting relevant information from target customers?",
      "answer": "Interview",
      "choices": [
        "Surveys",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Interview"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is typically done in person between the researcher/entrepreneur and a respondent where the researcher asks pertinent questions?",
      "answer": "Interview",
      "choices": [
        "Surveys",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Data Collection",
        "Interview"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the traditional method of conducting an interview?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What allows the researcher to establish relationship with potential participants and therefore gain their cooperation?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What generates the highest response rates in survey research?",
      "answer": "Personal interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Telephone interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Personal interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are less expensive and less time-consuming interviews?",
      "answer": "Telephone interviews",
      "choices": [
        "Personal interviews",
        "Focus Group Discussion",
        "Surveys",
        "Telephone interviews"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an excellent method for generating and screening ideas and concepts?",
      "answer": "Focus Group Discussion",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Surveys",
        "Data Collection",
        "Focus Group Discussion"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be moderated group interviews and brainstorming sessions that provide information on user's needs and behaviors?",
      "answer": "Focus Group Discussion",
      "choices": [
        "Interview",
        "Surveys",
        "Data Collection",
        "Focus Group Discussion"
      ],
      "reference": "Data Gathering Techniques",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a set of controllable and connected variables that a company gathers to satisfy a customer better than its competitor?",
      "answer": "Marketing Mix",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Place",
        "Marketing Mix"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to any goods or services that are produced to meet the consumers' wants, tastes and preferences?",
      "answer": "Product",
      "choices": [
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Product"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What represents the location where the buyer and seller exchange goods or services?",
      "answer": "Place",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Place"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another name for the location where the buyer and seller exchange goods or services?",
      "answer": "Distribution channel",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Price",
        "Promotion",
        "Distribution channel"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What typically buys and stores large quantities of several producers' goods and then breaks into bulk deliveries to supply retailers with smaller quantities?",
      "answer": "Wholesaler",
      "choices": [
        "Retailer",
        "Producer",
        "Consumer",
        "Wholesaler"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a company that buys products from a manufacturer or wholesaler and sells them to end users or customers?",
      "answer": "Retailer",
      "choices": [
        "Wholesaler",
        "Producer",
        "Consumer",
        "Retailer"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is another name for a channel that has no intermediary levels?",
      "answer": "Direct-marketing channel",
      "choices": [
        "Wholesaler",
        "Retailer",
        "Producer",
        "Direct-marketing channel"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the value of money in exchange for a product or service?",
      "answer": "Price",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Promotion",
        "Price"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What pricing strategy is used by businesses to attract customers to a new product or service by offering a lower price during its initial offering?",
      "answer": "Penetration Pricing",
      "choices": [
        "Skimming Pricing",
        "Cost-Plus Pricing",
        "Value-Based Pricing",
        "Penetration Pricing"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the complete set of activities, which communicate the product, brand or service to the user?",
      "answer": "Promotion",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Promotion"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What consists of each person who is involved in the product or service whether directly or indirectly?",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the outside appearance of a product and how it is presented to the customers?",
      "answer": "Packaging",
      "choices": [
        "Product",
        "Place",
        "Price",
        "Packaging"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to a process used by marketers to create an image in the minds of a target market?",
      "answer": "Positioning",
      "choices": [
        "Promotion",
        "Packaging",
        "People",
        "Positioning"
      ],
      "reference": "The 7Ps of Marketing",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a name, symbol, or other feature that distinguishes a seller's goods or services in the marketplace?",
      "answer": "Brand Name",
      "choices": [
        "Brand",
        "Branding Strategy",
        "Purpose",
        "Brand Name"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the customers' over-all experience of your business?",
      "answer": "Brand",
      "choices": [
        "Brand Name",
        "Branding Strategy",
        "Purpose",
        "Brand"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy focuses on financial success and value to the stakeholder?",
      "answer": "Purpose",
      "choices": [
        "Consistency",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility",
        "Purpose"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the significance of avoiding things that don't relate to or improve your brand?",
      "answer": "Consistency",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility",
        "Consistency"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy allows the customers have a chance to feel that they are part of your brand?",
      "answer": "Emotion",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Consistency",
        "Flexibility",
        "Emotion"
      ],
      "reference": "Brand",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What branding strategy allows you to adjust and differentiate your approach from your competition?",
      "answer": "Flexibility",
      "choices": [
        "Purpose",
        "Consistency",
        "Emotion",
        "Flexibility"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is equally important for your employees to be well versed in how they communicate with customers and represent the brand of your product?",
      "answer": "Employee Involvement",
      "choices": [
        "Loyalty",
        "Competitive Awareness",
        "Flexibility",
        "Employee Involvement"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an important part of brand strategy that sets the tone for what potential customers can expect?",
      "answer": "Loyalty",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Involvement",
        "Competitive Awareness",
        "Flexibility",
        "Loyalty"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should you not be frightened of and instead take as a challenge to improve your branding strategy?",
      "answer": "Competitive Awareness",
      "choices": [
        "Employee Involvement",
        "Loyalty",
        "Flexibility",
        "Competitive Awareness"
      ],
      "reference": "Branding",
      "term": "First Quarter"
    }
  ]
}
